Preiminary guide to the Rich Gold papers M1510
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 13: Xerox Parc
  - PARC - Overheads (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - The Workspace of the Future (theme overheads) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - The Novel and the Electrifying of its Collateral Cloud1996 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - The Creative Documents Initiative and the World Wide Web (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Proposal for the Creative Documents Laboratory (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Flyer - Call for Art, Photocopy Art Show1993 June (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Attitude Style (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - IBM Systems Journal (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - New York Times1991 August 15 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Recognition Award1999 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Booklets (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - CTheory (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Forward Anywhere (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Patents (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Mark Weiser (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Palo Alto Daily News (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - CDI (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Community of the Art (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - ParcTab (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - LiveBoard (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Fauxsters (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Talk (original)1991 June 20 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Spiel Pair Talk (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - PACT (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Early Tech Talk (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - 2 Heads (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Xerox Contract (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Xerox Ubi-Comp (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Xerox (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Photos (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Creative Documents Initiative Talk, Prints1996 February (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Some Thoughts on PAIR2001 October (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - PARC Forum "PAIR: The PARC Artist-In-Residence Program"1994 October 13 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Sketching a Vision (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - The Printing of Today Described in the Language of the Future1994 November (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - IACT Current1994 September 20 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - PACT (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - PARC/Goldstar (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - First TAB Report1991 July (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - PARC Aesthetic and Creative Technology Group1995 January 24 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - PAIR People (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - The Yellow Feather Mystery (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - UNIX (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Notes on IACT Talk1994 August 19 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - PARC 25th Anniversary1995 September 13 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Some New and Old Thoughts on PAIR2001 October (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Goldstar/Xerox Institute of Creative and Aesthetic Technology (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Art/Science/Design/Engineering (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Patents (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - The ParcTab Ubiquitous Computing Experiment (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Xerox Parc 25th Anniversary Third Decade Mid-decade Papers (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Research Group Achievement Award1993 (Box 53)
  - Corporate Research and Technology Special Recognition Award1999 (Box 53)
  - Recognition of drupa 2000 contributions2000 (Box 54)
  - Corporate Research Group Excellence in Science and Technology Award1992 (Box 82)
  - Corporate Research and Technology Special Recognition Award1998 (Box 82)
- Series 14: Videos
  - Adoption talk at PARC (Box 2)
  - Captain Power Bio Dread Strike Mission Skill Level: 2 (Box 2)
  - Video of "Little Computer People"1990 September 17 (Box 39)
  - Goldo 7 Demo1992 May (Box 39)
  - Harvey with GenLock1990 December 06 (Box 39)
  - PiouerBial Plain (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Fairy Go (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Moving Cities (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - XEN Direction '98: It's our company - Own IT! (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Little Computer People (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - ACM with James Burke: Beyond Cyberspace, ACM #1 with Jim Metcalfe (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - On Demand Machinery: Bookbinding Made Simple (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Turbulence-moments of, plus live interacive1995 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Kenny Rivaldo/M. Grossman (Box 41)
  - Kenny Rivaldo/M. Grossman (Box 41)
  - Allaire Galaire Audio Conference (Box 41)
  - Xerox CEO's Report Video1996 November (Box 41)
  - Interactive Emergent (Box 41)
  - Tokyo Rose1994 (Box 41)
  - LiveBoard in the Classroom1994 November (Box 41)
  - PARC "Focus Plus Context Displays"2001 May 11 (Box 41)
  - PARC "JSB Tribute Event"2000 June 16 (Box 41)
  - Xerox CEO Report Video1995 November (Box 41)
  - ARS Electronica Center (Box 41)
  - Peter Jennings' ABC News XFR Segment (Box 41)
  - (Box 42)
  - The Computer: A Tool for Sculptors 1992 (Box 42)
  - Xerox "3 Xerox Commercials: Jack's story; Alice's Story; Ollendorf's Story" (Box 42)
  - Tech Demos (Box 42)
  - Party (Box 42)
  - Hakari - Ubi Coffer - (ABC) Air Jet (Box 42)
  - Office Design Project (Box 42)
  - PARC "Comdex '98 Keynote Rick Thoman, John Seely Brown"1998 November 20 (Box 42)
  - Inside Business NBC/KRON TV (Box 42)
  - Sheldon Brown "Assorted Works" (Box 42)
  - Jim Campbell "Video Documentation" (Box 42)
  - Catherine Richard (Box 42)
  - PARC Forum "PAIR"1998 October 18 (Box 43)
  - PARC Overview and Status of the Internet Business Opportunities Task Force1996 February 02 (Box 43)
  - Playing With Toy Interfaces1990 September 27 (Box 43)
  - PARC Forum "Seven Pragmas of Inovation"1998 October 08 (Box 43)
  - The CEO's Report1997 May (Box 44)
  - Virtual Reality Compilation1990 (Box 44)
  - Robot Loop to Snake Transition1999 November 12 (Box 44)
  - Reality Built for Two I'm a Little Robot1989 (Box 44)
  - PARC Identity Workshop1996 (Box 44)
  - The Autodesk Cyberspace Project (Box 44)
  - History of Xerox 1906-1984 (Box 44)
  - Media Lab Colloquium with Rich Gold2001 March 28 (Box 44)
  - Music Animation Machine1990 (Box 44)
  - T. V. Commercials (Box 44)
  - United States Coast Guard Futech Tape 4 of 4 (Box 45)
  - From Atoms to Cultures A Visit to PARC1992 April 10 (Box 45)
  - XFR Compilation 8 Prototypes, ABC News, MediaWest, The XFR Design Story [1 of 2] (Box 45)
  - XFR Compilation 8 Prototypes, ABC News, MediaWest, The XFR Design Story [2 of 2] (Box 45)
  - Re: Reading Dispatches from XFR Museum Musings by the Members of RED2000 March 23 (Box 45)
  - Experiments in the Future of Reading1999 March 13 (Box 45)
  - PARC 25 Event CEO Paul Allaire, intro Rich Gold (Box 45)
  - It's More than Paper, It's Electric Paper!1996 May 19 (Box 45)
  - PAIR: The First Year1994 October 13 (Box 45)
  - Xerox PARC: 25th Anniversary Celebration Part 1 of 21995 September 25 (Box 45)
  - Xerox PARC: 25th Anniversary Celebration Part 2 of 21995 September 25 (Box 45)
  - PAIR.93.3.30.1 (Box 46)
  - Reflection Technology VR Demo (Box 46)
  - Reading from Loglan1990 (Box 46)
  - Canada Council for the Arts (Box 46)
  - SEGA Masters of the Universe Star Trek1985 (Box 46)
  - Fragment of a Talk by Rich Gold (Box 46)
  - PAL Low File 13 (Box 46)
  - Experiments in the Future of Reading1999 September 10 (Box 46)
  - Van den Doel & Pail (Box 46)
  - Comdex '98 Highlights1998 December 17 (Box 46)
  - Epileptograph "With Titles and Credits" (Box 46)
  - Captain Power (Box 46)
  - Comdex B-roll E-Tag document, Tilt, and E-Tag Translation1998 November 10 (Box 46)
- Series 15: Reviews
  - Computer Music Journal vol 10 no 21986 (Box 47)
  - Keyboard vol 20 no 91994 September (Box 47)
  - Fortune vol 130 no 11994 July 11 (Box 47)
  - The International Design Magazine (copy)2001 June (Box 47)
  - Dr. Dobb's Journal Special Report 2000 December (Box 47)
  - NXN (Box 47)
  - Time2000 December 04 (Box 47)
  - Das Kölner Design Jahrbuch 1995 (Box 47)
  - Art Hansa Special (Box 47)
  - Design Institute (Box 47)
  - Midtown Crossings Workshop (Box 47)
  - Fröken Julie provutgäva (Box 47)
  - Computer Music Journal vol 2 no 3 (Box 47)
  - West1995 August 27 (Box 47)
  - EAR vol 6 no 51978 (Box 47)
  - Commodore Microcomputers vol 7 no 21986 April (Box 47)
  - Commodore vol 4 no 61986 January (Box 47)
  - Compute!'s Gazette issue 34 vol 4 no 41986 April (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - 16 Publications (Box 48)
- Series 16: Toys
  - Baby Heather (Box 49)
  - Captain Power (Box 49)
  - AIR (Artificially Intelligent Robot) (Box 50)
  - Elly the Elephant (Box 50)
  - Power Glove (Box 50)
  - Wheel of Fortune (Box 50)
- Series 17: Posters
  - 7 Posters (Othertype 1)
  - Able Was I Print Master (Othertype 1)
- Series: 18 Discs
  - Discs (24) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Series 19: Audio
  - loudSPIRE (Box 2)
  - Rich Gold 6 Trak (Box 2)
  - Famous Computer Cafe Little C. People1986 January 02 (Box 2)
  - Sega Dgital Sound Effects1985 (Box 2)
  - Rocker Tape (Box 2)
  - Speech Systems/6 Trak (Box 2)
  - Daddy-YDad Sampled Sound (Box 2)